# ITAI MIZLISH

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT



+97254-2258899



itaim148@gmail.com



in www.linkedin.com/in/itai-mizlish/



https://github.com/itaim18



www.itaimiz.com

# EDUCATION

**Bachelor in Science in Computer** Science

**JCT Lev Academic Center** 

2015 - 2019

# CERTIFICATES

- The complete 2022 Web development Bootcamp.
- · React The Complete Guide.
- · JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass

| udemy

# SKILLS

- React
- JavaScript & ES6
- HTML5
- CSS3/ Sass
- Redux & React Query
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- Typescript
- Firebase
- express
- Tailwind
- MERN stack

#### PROFILE

I am a Frontend Developer and a Fullstack developer with a strong understanding of React.js, its cores and hooks with close to 230 hours of courses I took to explore this subject. Knowledgeable in DS implementation and algorithms solving in JavaScript and ES6. Experienced in building Frontend and Fullstack architectures from scratch. I'm a Computer Science graduate in the age of 19 and a self learner. A team player who loves to share his aspects on code a problem-solver and thrives on criticism.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Frontend/Fullstack Developer

2022 - present

- Design and create architectures for web applications.
- Develop full-stack web apps using MERN structure and firebase.
- Using Javascript libraries, CSS and Sass to create user interfaces.
- · Experience in functional programming in JavaScript and knowledgeable in ES6.
- · using React libraries like react-router and Redux and expanding my work to libraries such as React Query, MUI, react-hook-form etc.

**Tutor** 2016 - 2018

Israeli Center for Advancement in Math (associated with Bar Ilan University)

- Facilitated annual Science Day activities for children.
- Tutored basic Physics and Aeronautics lessons in schools in the TA Metropolitan Area.
- · Graded tests and tutored children with special needs.

# **Military Service**

2019 - 2022

Infantry Unit

# **Volunteering**

2015 - 2018

Krembo Wings

· Assisted and accompanied children with special needs and formed unique connections with them.

# LANGUAGES

English

Hebrew

